A Guide to the Fries Textile Plant Records, 1900-1988
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series I: Company Files, 1908-1979
  - Southern Oxygen Co., October- December 1956 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Standard Chemical Products Inc., August 1956 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - States Marine Lines Isthmian Lines, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Steel Heddle Mfg. Co., January- October 1956 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - W. L. Stewart Co., August- September 1956 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Superior-Sterling Co., 1956 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Miscellaneous "T", January- September 1956 (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Taylor Instrument Companies, July- November 1956 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - The Terrell Machine Co., May- August 1956 (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Textile Fibre Spray, Inc., March- April 1956 (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Tidewater Supply Co., Inc., September 1956 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Traffic Department, October- December 1956 (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Traffic Department, July- September 1956 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Traffic Department, April- June 1956 (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Traffic Department, January- March 1956 (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - S. J. Tutag and Co., July- August 1956 (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - Miscellaneous "U", January- November 1956 (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - The United Iron and Metal Co., May- November 1956 (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - United Mills Corporation, January- June 1956 (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, January- February 1956 (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - U.S Dept. of the Interior, December 1955- April 1956 (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - U.S. Rubber Co., April 1956 (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - Utility Supply Co., March 1956 (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Miscellaneous "V", 1956 (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - Victor Ring Traveler Co., April- December 1956 (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Dept. of Conservation and Development, May 1956 (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - Commonwealth of Va Dept. of Health, December 1955- December 1956 (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - Commonwealth of Va. Dept. of Highways, June- November 1956 (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Department of Labor and Industry, May- December 1956 (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia State Registration Board for Contractors, May 1956 (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - Commonwealth of Va (Delinquent Tax Col.), January- February 1956 (Box 13, Folder 98)
  - Commonwealth of Va. Va. State Ports Authority, October- November 1956 (Box 13, Folder 99)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Dept. of Taxation, February- May 1956 (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Unemployment Compensation Commission, January- October 1956 (Box 155, Folder 17)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Dept. of Workmen's Compensation, June- October 1956 (Box 13, Folder 102)
  - Virginia Council on Health and Medical Care, January 1955- November 1956 (Box 13, Folder 103)
  - Virginia Manufacturers Association, January- July 1956 (Box 13, Folder 104)
  - Virginia Safety Association, January- February 1956 (Box 13, Folder 105)
  - Va. Society for Crippled Children and Adults, May- August 1956 (Box 13, Folder 106)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, July- September 1956 (Box 13, Folder 107)
  - Va. State Weights and Measures Sec., February 1956 (Box 13, Folder 108)
  - Miscellaneous "W", 1956 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Waddell Hospital, September 1956 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Walker Bros. and Co., Ltd., February- September 1956 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Washington Mills Co., January- March 1956 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Washington Mills Co., April- June 1956 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Washington Mills Co., July- September 1956 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Washington Mills Co., October- December 1956 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Werther Bag Corporation, January- September 1956 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Westbrook Elevator Mfg. Co., September- December 1956 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Western Carloading Co., April 1956 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corp., January- May 1956 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Whitin Machine Works, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Wilson Exterminating Co., Inc., March- April 1956 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Thomas C. Wilson, Inc., July 1956 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous "X, Y, Z", May- November 1956 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous "L", March- November 1957 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Leslie and Co., February 1957 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Leslie and Co., January 1957 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Wilson Lewith, November 1957 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Linde Company, September 1957 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Lockwood Greene Engineers Architects, November- December 1957 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Logan Company, September- October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Lombard Governor Co., October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - The Longman Mfg. Co., November 1957 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Link-Belt Co., February- November 1957 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Lyman Printing and Finishing Co., March- April 1957 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous "Mc", April- August 1957 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Lynchburg Iron and Metal Co., February- December 1957 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Mr. James D. McBride, May- June 1957 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - McLean Trucking Co., May- August 1957 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous "M", 1957 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Malone Freight Lines, Inc., January- October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Manton-Gaulin, March- June 1957 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Maryland Casualty Co., August 1956- December 1957 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Matson Steamship Co., April- October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Meadows Manufacturing Co., October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - G. A. Mosites Co., January 1957 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Mundy Motor Lines, January- October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous "N", March- December 1957 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Nachman Corp., March 1957 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - National Cash Register Co., January- June 1957 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - New York and New Jersey Lubricant Co., January- September 1957 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Norfolk and Western Railway Co., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - North Carolina State College, August- September 1957 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - North Electric Co., August- October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Miscellaneous "O", November- December 1957 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Odell Mill Supply Co., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - O'Hanlon-Watson Drug Co., Inc., February- June 1957 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Olin Mathieson Chemical Corp., January- February 1957 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Orkin Exterminating Co., Inc., February- May 1957 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Miscellaneous "P", 1957 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Parks-Cramer Co., May- November 1957 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Joel S. Perkins and Son, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Piedmont Mountain Freight Lines, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Pioneer Carloading Co., May- June 1957 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Plymouth Rubber Co., October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Pressure Concrete Co., February- March 1957 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Product Sales, Inc., February- September 1957 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Miscellaneous "R", 1957 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Remington Rand (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Republic Textile Co., March- April 1957 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - J. E. Rhoads and Sons, March 1957 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Roanoke Engineering Sales Co., January 1957 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Rock Hill Printing and Fin. Co., March- November 1957 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Ross- Meehan Foundries, January 1957 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Royal Netherlands Steamship Co., July- October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Mrs. Leonard Rubright, October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Miscellaneous "S", January- December 1957 (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - Saco-Lowell Shops, May- December 1957 (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - Salem Steel Co., July- October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - Schmidt Mfg. Co. of S.C., January- April 1957 (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - Scott Testers (Southern) Inc., March 1957 (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - Security Life and Trust Co., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - Seneca Textile Co., June 1957 (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - Seydel-Woolley and Co., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - Signode Steel Strapping Co., March- December 1957 (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - Slaughter Machinery Co., April 1957 (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - Slip-Not Belting Co., January- October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 78)
  - John Smith and Son, March- July 1957 (Box 14, Folder 79)
  - Sonoco Products Co., April- August 1957 (Box 14, Folder 80)
  - Southeastern Missouri Congress Co., September 1957 (Box 14, Folder 81)
  - Southern Fuel Oils Inc., December 1957 (Box 14, Folder 82)
  - Southern Meter and Supply Co., January- November 1957 (Box 14, Folder 83)
  - Standard Textile Machine Works, February- August 1957 (Box 14, Folder 84)
  - States-Marine-Isthmian Agency, Inc., February- October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 85)
  - Steel Heddle Mfg. Co., March- July 1957 (Box 14, Folder 86)
  - Hugh G. Strickland, Inc., March- April 1957 (Box 14, Folder 87)
  - Stonhard Co, Inc., October- November 1957 (Box 14, Folder 88)
  - Strother Drug Co., July 1957 (Box 14, Folder 89)
  - Stowe-Woodward, Inc., October- November 1957 (Box 14, Folder 90)
  - W. H. Sullivan Company, April 1957 (Box 14, Folder 91)
  - Superior-Sterling Co., February- December 1957 (Box 14, Folder 92)
  - Taylor Instrument Companies, April- June 1957 (Box 14, Folder 93)
  - Time Loan Co., May 1957 (Box 14, Folder 94)
  - Terrell Machine Co., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 95)
  - Teletex Corp., September 1957 (Box 14, Folder 96)
  - Alvin Teat and Co., September- October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 97)
  - Traffic Department, January- March 1957 (Box 14, Folder 98)
  - Traffic Department, April- June 1957 (Box 14, Folder 99)
  - Traffic Department, July- September 1957 (Box 14, Folder 100)
  - Traffic Department, October- December 1957 (Box 14, Folder 101)
  - True Wall Steel Co., October 1956- March 1957 (Box 14, Folder 102)
  - Miscellaneous "U", May- June 1957 (Box 14, Folder 103)
  - United Iron and Metal Co., February- December 1957 (Box 14, Folder 104)
  - United Mills Corp., December 1956- January 1957 (Box 14, Folder 105)
  - U.S. Government- Treasury Dept., September- October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 106)
  - U.S. Rubber Company, January- August 1957 (Box 14, Folder 107)
  - Uster Corp., May- November 1957 (Box 14, Folder 108)
  - Miscellaneous "V", February- December 1957 (Box 14, Folder 109)
  - Va. Dept. of Conservation and Development, October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 110)
  - Valley Roofing Co., February 1957 (Box 14, Folder 111)
  - Vamco Chemical Co. Inc., January 1957 (Box 14, Folder 112)
  - Veeder-Root, Inc., March- October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 113)
  - Verd-A-Ray Corp., April 1957 (Box 14, Folder 114)
  - Veterans Administration, February- August 1957 (Box 14, Folder 115)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Miscellaneous, October- November 1957 (Box 14, Folder 116)
  - Virginia Council on Health and Medical Care, February- December 1957 (Box 14, Folder 117)
  - Virginia Foundation for Independent Colleges, October- November 1957 (Box 14, Folder 118)
  - Virginia Manufacturers Association, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 119)
  - Virginia Society for Crippled Children and Adults, June- October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 120)
  - Commonwealth of Va. Dept. of Education, July 1957 (Box 14, Folder 121)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Dept. of Health, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 122)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Dept. of Highways, April- August 1957 (Box 14, Folder 123)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Dept. of Labor and Industry, January- October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 124)
  - Commonwealth of Virginia Unemployment Compensation Commission, March 1957- March 1958 (Box 14, Folder 125)
  - Miscellaneous "W", 1957 (Box 14, Folder 126)
  - Washington Mills Co., January- March 1957 (Box 14, Folder 127)
  - Washington Mills Co., April- June 1957 (Box 14, Folder 128)
  - Washington Mills Co., July- September 1957 (Box 14, Folder 129)
  - Washington Mills Co., October- December 1957 (Box 14, Folder 130)
  - Watson Desmond, Inc., January- September 1957 (Box 14, Folder 131)
  - Wayne Manufacturing Co., September- October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 132)
  - Werthan Bag Corp., January 1957 (Box 14, Folder 133)
  - West Disinfecting Co., March 1957 (Box 14, Folder 134)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corp., August 1957 (Box 14, Folder 135)
  - West Point Foundry and Machine Co., January- October 1957 (Box 14, Folder 136)
  - Whitin Machine Works, February- December 1957 (Box 14, Folder 137)
  - Miss Rosalind Williams, September 1957 (Box 14, Folder 138)
  - Miscellaneous X, Y, Z, December 1957 (Box 14, Folder 139)
  - Yeomans Textile Machinery Co., February- March 1957 (Box 14, Folder 140)
  - Leslie, Catlin and Co., January 1958 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Leslie, Catlin and Co. Inc., February 1958 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Leslie, Catlin and Co. Inc, March 1958 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Wilson Lewith Machinery Corp., September- October 1958 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Lockwood, Greene Engineers, January- March 1958 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - C. H. Long, September- October 1958 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Lyman Printing and Finishing, March- December 1958 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Lynchburg Foundry Co., January- February 1958 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Lynchburg Iron and Metal Co., March- October 1958 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous M, June- December 1961 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Malone Freight Lines, March 1958 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Manton-Gaulin Mfg. Co., June- November 1958 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Chas. J. Main Inc., June- December 1958 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Dr. Johannes Marinus, January- February 1958 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Maryland Casualty Co., 1958 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Masury-Young Co., September- December 1958 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Matson S.S. Co., May- June 1958 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Meadows Manufacturing Co., May- July 1958 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Medley Manufacturing Co., September- November 1958 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Moffett and Klein Corp., February 1958 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Monroe Calculating Mch. Co., March- November 1958 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Mundy Motor Lines, January- November 1958 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Mill-Power Supply Co., March 1958 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous "N", March- September 1958 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Nachman Corp., May 1958 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - National Carloading Co., 1958 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - National Cash Register, March- November 1958 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - National Electric Coil, March- July 1958 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - National Foremen's Institute, March- June 1958 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - National Springs Corp., March- December 1958 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Neptune Meter Co., March- August 1958 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - New York and New Jersey Lubricant Co., 1958 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Norfolk and Western Rwy. Co., 1958 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - North Electric Co., January- July 1958 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - North Carolina State College, April 1958 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous O, February- September 1958 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - The O'Brien Machinery Co., February- May 1958 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Oil City Glass Co., July 1958 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Odell Mill Supply Co., January- September 1958 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous P, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Pacific Mills Domestics Corp., October- November 1958 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Joel S. Perkins and Son, January- April 1958 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - R. L. Persinger and Co., June- July 1958 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Piedmont Mountain Freight Lines, March- November 1958 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Hugh Pinnix Realty Co., January- September 1958 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Pioneer Bag Co., February- June 1958 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Pittsburgh Steel, March 1958 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Pleasants Hardware Co., December 1958 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Plymouth Rubber Co., May- December 1958 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Pomona Foundry, April- May 1958 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Pope and Talbot Lines, May- November 1958 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - M. M. Price, March 1958 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Progressive Machine Co., June 1958 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Miscellaneous Q, March- June 1958 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Queen City Foundry, April- June 1958 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Miscellaneous R, February- December 1958 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Redfield Company (Cabin Crafts, Inc), June 1958 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Dr. C.W. Richardson, May- December 1958 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Reserve Life Ins. Co., March 1958 (Box 155, Folder 18)
  - Hoyt A. Ridenhour, April- May 1958 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Rock Hill Print and Fin. Co., February- September 1958 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - E. F. Rose Co., April- July 1958 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - F. H. Ross and Co., February- August 1958 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Miscellaneous S, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Saco-Lowell Shops, February- December 1958 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - St. Louis Button Co Inc, August 1958 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Sanitized Sales Co. of America Inc, January- August 1958 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Scott Testers, Inc., February- May 1958 (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Seaboard Air Line Rwy. Co., April 1958 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Secuirty Life and Trust Co, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Semmes Bag Co., 1958 (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Service Appliance Co., April- December 1958 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Seydel-Woolley Co., February- October 1958 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Signode Steel Strapping Co., April- December 1958 (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Simplex Valve and Meter Co., October 1958- January 1959 (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - SKF Industries, Inc., September 1958 (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - Eugene B. Smith Co. Inc., April- December 1958 (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - Smith-Courtney Co., May- June 1958 (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - Socony Mobil Oil Co./ Socony Vacuum Oil Co., January- September 1958 (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - Southern Loom Reed, February 1958 (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - Southern Meter and Supply Co., February- July 1958 (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - Southern Oxygen, May- June 1958 (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - A. E. Staley Mfg. Co., January- November 1958 (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - Standard Elec. Mfg. Co., May 1958 (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - States-Marine Isthmian Agency, January- November 1958 (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - Steel Heddle Mfg. Co. Stedco- Southern, Inc., February- October 1958 (Box 15, Folder 86)
  - Superior- Sterling Co., January- November 1958 (Box 15, Folder 87)
  - Sure-Fit Products Co., November 1958 (Box 15, Folder 88)
  - P. O. Stribling, Jr., September- October 1958 (Box 15, Folder 89)
  - Miscellaneous T, January- November 1958 (Box 15, Folder 90)
  - Shirley Taylor, June- July 1958 (Box 15, Folder 91)
  - Thonet Industries, Inc., February- March 1958 (Box 15, Folder 92)
  - The Tire Mart, June- July 1958 (Box 15, Folder 93)
  - Toledo Scales Co., April- November 1958 (Box 15, Folder 94)
  - Ton-Tex Corp., November 1958 (Box 15, Folder 95)
  - Traffic Department, January- March 1958 (Box 15, Folder 96)
  - Traffic Department, April- June 1958 (Box 15, Folder 97)
  - Traffic Department, July- September 1958 (Box 15, Folder 98)
  - Traffic Dept., October- December 1958 (Box 15, Folder 99)
  - Miscellaneous U, June 1958 (Box 15, Folder 100)
  - United Iron and Metal Co., June 1958 (Box 15, Folder 101)
  - U.S. Rubber Co., January- February 1958 (Box 15, Folder 102)
  - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, May- December 1958 (Box 15, Folder 103)
  - United Merchants and Manufacturers, June- July 1958 (Box 15, Folder 104)
  - U.S. Testing Co., April- November 1958 (Box 15, Folder 105)
  - Uster Corporation, March- December 1958 (Box 15, Folder 106)
  - Miscellaneous V, February- October 1958 (Box 15, Folder 107)
  - Veeder Root, Inc., July- August 1958 (Box 15, Folder 108)
  - Veterans Administration, January- July 1958 (Box 15, Folder 109)
  - Virginia Council on Health and Medical Care Doctors, December 1957- January 1958 (Box 15, Folder 110)
  - Virginia Division of Forestry, December 1958 (Box 15, Folder 111)
  - Virginia Council Health and Medical Care, December 1957- February 1960 (Box 15, Folder 112)
  - Va. Society for Crippled Children Camp Easter Seal, April- May 1958 (Box 15, Folder 113)
  - Southwestern State Hosp. Comm. of Virginia, August- October 1958 (Box 155, Folder 19)
  - Virginia (State Board of Health) Dept. of Health, January- September 1958 (Box 15, Folder 115)
  - Virginia Dept of Highways, August 1958 (Box 15, Folder 116)
  - Comm. of Va. Industrial Commission of Virginia, January 1958 (Box 15, Folder 117)
  - Virginia Manufacturers Assoc., January- October 1958 (Box 15, Folder 118)
  - Comm. of Va. Unemployment Compensation Commission, January- November 1958 (Box 15, Folder 119)
  - Miscellaneous W, January- July 1958 (Box 15, Folder 120)
  - Waddell Hospital, April- May 1958 (Box 15, Folder 121)
  - Washington Mills Co., January- March 1958 (Box 15, Folder 122)
  - Washington Mills Co., April- June 1958 (Box 15, Folder 123)
  - Washington Mills Co., July- September 1958 (Box 15, Folder 124)
  - Washington Mills Co., October- December 1958 (Box 15, Folder 125)
  - Watson and Desmond, February- October 1958 (Box 15, Folder 126)
  - Weber Marking Systems, May- October 1958 (Box 15, Folder 127)
  - Werthan Bag Corp., January- July 1958 (Box 15, Folder 128)
  - Westbrook Elevator Mfg. Co., June 1958 (Box 15, Folder 129)
  - Westinghouse Electric Supply Co./ Westinghouse Elec. Corp., February- November 1958 (Box 15, Folder 130)
  - Whitin Machine Works, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 131)
  - Woods and Gleaves, June 1958 (Box 15, Folder 132)
  - Wythe County Court August, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 133)
  - George Wythe High School, January- February 1958 (Box 15, Folder 134)
  - State of West Virginia Dept of Archives and History, July- November 1958 (Box 15, Folder 135)
  - Miscellaneous X Y Z, March- December 1958 (Box 15, Folder 136)
  - Wytheville Block Co., January- June 1958 (Box 15, Folder 137)
  - Town of Wytheville, March 1958 (Box 15, Folder 138)
  - Armstrong Cork Company, October 1970 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Ashworth Bros, Inc., January- November 1970 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Associated Sprinkler Co., May 1970 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Astrup Company, July 1970 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Atlanta Belting Co., January- September 1970 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Atlanta Brush Company, February- December 1970 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Atlas Supply Company (folder 1 of 2), January 1969- December 1970 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Atlas Supply Company (folder 2 of 2), January 1969- December 1970 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Autocon Industries, Inc., September 1970 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Bahan Textile Machy Co, Inc, January 1970- October 1971 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - The Bahnson Company, November 1967- July 1970 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Baltimore Business Forms, August 1970 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Barber-Coleman Company, November 1967- January 1971 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Louis P. Batson Co., November 1970 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Batson Yarn and Fabrics Machy., April- November 1970 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Batson Warp Tying Machy. Inc., February- December 1970 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Beemer Engineering Co., September 1970 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - The Bemis Company, April- December 1970 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Bendix Scientific Instrument and Equip. Div., August- October 1970 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - B-I-F Industries, January- June 1970 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - BiJur Lubricating Corp., August- December 1970 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Bilco Manufacturing Corp., March- December 1970 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Black and Decker Mfg. Co., August 1967- September 1970 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Blue Ridge Evergreen Co., October 1970 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Blue Ridge Office Equip., June 1970- November 1971 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - R. H. Bouligny Co., June- December 1970 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Brass and Copper Supply Co., January- June 1970 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Bristol Steel and Iron Works Inc., March 1970 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Brown Grease Gun Co., Inc., 1970 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Bureau of Business Practice, November 1970 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Carolina Loom Reed Co., September 1969- March 1970 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Carolina Roller and Supply, October 1970 (Box 16, Folder 32)